What is PayNow? PayNow is a fast and secure way to transfer funds using just a mobile number or NRIC.
Where can I find my account balance in the OCBC App? You can find it on the home screen under 'Account Overview'.
What is the daily transaction limit for OCBC Internet Banking? The daily transaction limit is $10,000.
How do I secure my OCBC App? Enable two-factor authentication and keep your password confidential.
How do I change a daily transaction limit via the OCBC app? Step 1: Log in to the OCBC app Step 2: Tap on the "More" icon in the bottom navigation bar > Card Services > Manage card limit Step 3: Review and confirm the new limit Step 4: Authorise the change using OCBC OneToken (on your mobile device) or your hardware token
What is the authorisation limit used for? If a transaction amount is equal to or above the authorisation limit, you will be required to authorise the transaction using your fully activated OCBC OneToken or hardware token.
Is the authorisation limit the same as the daily transaction limit? No, they are different limits. The daily transaction limit refers to the total amount which you can pay or transfer each day. You can set your daily transaction limit for funds transfers/payments according to your preference. The authorisation limit applies to each transaction you make. If the transaction amount is equal to or above the authorisation limit, you will be required to authorise the transaction using your fully activated OCBC OneToken or hardware token. The authorisation limit is fixed and cannot be changed.
What is “Your activity” on the Account Summary dashboard? You can view all your latest transactions across all your Current, Savings and card accounts at one glance in “Your activity”. This includes your last 7 transactions from the past 7 days (including today). Tap on “See more” to view all transactions from the past 7 days. You may also tap on a transaction to view more details, as well as links to actions such as viewing overall spending activity on Money Insights or to Raise a dispute (applicable for credit cards). Please note that only posted transactions will appear in “Your activity”, as well as in account transaction history (see point 5 below). There may be a lead time between when the transaction is performed and shown on the dashboard.
How do I view my transaction history for individual accounts from the Account Summary dashboard? You can view details and transaction history (past 6 months) of individual accounts through either of these: Tap on What you have / What you owe > Select a Current/Savings account or card Tap on “See more” beside “Your activity” > Tap on the filter button beside “View all transactions” > Select a Current/Savings account or card
How do I enable text-to-speech? On the homepage, press the Volume icon to enable the test-to-speech function.
How do I use the magnifying function? Please press the magnifying glass icon on the top right of the page.
How do I contact manual support? Please contact us using the built in video call function, or consider contacting us on our offical website at https://www.ocbc.com/personal-banking/help-and-support
Where do I find the walkthrough function? On the homepage, please press the guide button on the bottom left.